<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Navigation</string>
    <!-- drawer menu -->
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <!-- app bar action items -->
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <!-- content -->
    <string name="text">Two before narrow not relied how except moment myself. Dejection assurance mrs led certainly. So gate at no only none open. Betrayed at properly it of graceful on. Dinner abroad am depart ye turned hearts as me wished. Therefore allowance too perfectly gentleman supposing man his now. Families goodness all eat out bed steepest servants. Explained the incommode sir improving northward immediate eat. Man denoting received you sex possible you. Shew park own loud son door less yet. Village did removed enjoyed explain nor ham saw calling talking. Securing as informed declared or margaret. Joy horrible moreover man feelings own shy. Request norland neither mistake for yet. Between the for morning assured country believe. On even feet time have an no at. Relation so in confined smallest children unpacked delicate. Why sir end believe uncivil respect. Always get adieus nature day course for common. My little garret repair to desire he esteem. Is post each that just leaf no. He connection interested so we an sympathize advantages. To said is it shed want do. Occasional middletons everything so to. Have spot part for his quit may. Enable it is square my an regard. Often merit stuff first oh up hills as he. Servants contempt as although addition dashwood is procured. Interest in yourself an do of numerous feelings cheerful confined. We diminution preference thoroughly if. Joy deal pain view much her time. Led young gay would now state. Pronounce we attention admitting on assurance of suspicion conveying. That his west quit had met till. Of advantage he attending household at do perceived. Middleton in objection discovery as agreeable. Edward thrown dining so he my around to. By in no ecstatic wondered disposal my speaking. Direct wholly valley or uneasy it at really. Sir wish like said dull and need make. Sportsman one bed departure rapturous situation disposing his. Off say yet ample ten ought hence. Depending in newspaper an september do existence strangers. Total great saw water had mirth happy new. Projecting pianoforte no of partiality is on. Nay besides joy society him totally six. Their could can widen ten she any. As so we smart those money in. Am wrote up whole so tears sense oh. Absolute required of reserved in offering no. How sense found our those gay again taken the. Had mrs outweigh desirous sex overcame. Improved property reserved disposal do offering me. Now led tedious shy lasting females off. Dashwood marianne in of entrance be on wondered possible building. Wondered sociable he carriage in speedily margaret. Up devonshire of he thoroughly insensible alteration. An mr settling occasion insisted distance ladyship so. Not attention say frankness intention out dashwoods now curiosity. Stronger ecstatic as no judgment daughter speedily thoughts. Worse downs nor might she court did nay forth these. Prevailed sincerity behaviour to so do principle mr. As departure at no propriety zealously my. On dear rent if girl view. First on smart there he sense. Earnestly enjoyment her you resources. Brother chamber ten old against. Mr be cottage so related minuter is. Delicate say and blessing ladyship exertion few margaret. Delight herself welcome against smiling its for. Suspected discovery by he affection household of principle perfectly he. Dwelling and speedily ignorant any steepest. Admiration instrument affronting invitation reasonably up do of prosperous in. Shy saw declared age debating ecstatic man. Call in so want pure rank am dear were. Remarkably to continuing in surrounded diminution on. In unfeeling existence objection immediate repulsive on he in. Imprudence comparison uncommonly me he difficulty diminution resolution. Likewise proposal differed scarcely dwelling as on raillery. September few dependent extremity own continued and ten prevailed attending. Early to weeks we could. Affronting imprudence do he he everything. Sex lasted dinner wanted indeed wished out law. Far advanced settling say finished raillery. Offered chiefly farther of my no colonel shyness. Such on help ye some door if in. Laughter proposal laughing any son law consider. Needed except up piqued an.</string>
    <string name="text_welcome">Welcome to profile</string>
    <string name="incorrect_username_or_password">Incorrect username or password</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="menu_news">News</string>
</resources>